Guide to the Brooklyn location scouting photographs collection CBHM.0017
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 38: Red Hook, circa 1990 - 2011
  - EXT Dock Front Warehouse, Port Authority, 90 Columbia Street, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Erie Basin Bargeport, 700 Columbia Street, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - INT/EXT Dockfront Warehouse, Erie Basin Bargeport, 700 Columbia Street, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Abandoned School and Lot, Red Hook, Conover Street between Sullivan Street and Wolcott Street, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - End of Van Brunt Street, Red Hook [Waterfront Barge Museum], 1994 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - NY Shipyard Corporation, 1 Bear Street, Red Hook, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - EXT Loft, Beard Street warehouses, Red Hook, circa 1995 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Red Hook warehouse, circa 1995 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Beard Street at Van Brunt Street, circa 1995 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Bush Terminal, Red Hook [Camelot Supper Club], circa 1995 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - EXT Highway, Brooklyn Battery Tunnel, circa 1995 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Abandoned street, Beard Street between Richards Street and Dwight Street, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Various streets, Red Hook, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    This folder includes photographs of Pioneer Street (between Richards Street and Van Brunt Street), Dikeman Street (between Dwight Street and Richards Street), Coffey Street (between Ferris Street and Conover Street).
  - EXT Truck Yard, Pier 41 Associates, 204-207 Van Brunt Street, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - INT Seedy Hotel, 417 Van Brunt Street at Beard Street, Apt. 2L, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - EXT Truck Yard, Red Hook Marine Terminal, American Stevedoring Inc., Foot of Hamilton Avenue, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - INT Stage, 1 Beard Street, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - House - J-Mac's - EXT only, 27 Wolcott Street (between Richards Street and Dwight Street), Red Hook, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 318 Van Brunt Avenue (between Verona Street and Pioneer Street), Red Hook, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - INT/EXT House - J-Mac's, 123 Pioneer Street (between Van Brunt Street and Richards Street), Red Hook, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 392 Van Brunt Street (corner of Dikeman Street), Red Hook, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Gas Station, Commerce Street and Hamilton Avenue, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - INT Prison courtyard, New York Shipyard, 1 Beard Street, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Mona's Space, Pier 12, Red Hook, circa 2000 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - EXT Wading Pool, Red Hook Rec Area, Clinton Street and Lorraine Street, circa 2000 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    This folder was categorized under "Parks, Housing Projects, Hospitals, Apt. Towers, Retirement Homes."
  - INT/EXT Dockfront warehouse, Red Hook Container Terminal, Universal Maritime Service Corporation, Van Brunt Street and Hamilton Avenue, circa 2000 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - New York Shipyard, 1 Beard Street, Red Hook, circa 2000 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Mona's Space, Goltens, 160 Van Brunt Street, circa 2000 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Bar, Sunny's / John's Bar, Conover Street between Beard Street and Reade Street, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - New York Shipyard, 1 Beard Street, Red Hook, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - INT Warehouse, Cornerstone Warehouse 8A, Pier 41, foot of Van Brunt Street, Red Hook, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - INT/EXT Warehouse, New York Shipyard, Industrial building, Beard Street, Red Hook, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Revere Sugar Factory, Beard Street at Richards Street, Red Hook, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Loft/courtyard, Pier 41, Beard Street, Red Hook, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Loft/courtyard, New York Shipyard, Beard Street, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - EXT Apartment Building, Conover Street at Coffey Street, Red Hook, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Red Hook and Columbia Heights Neighborhood, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    This folder includes photographs of Dwight Street and Beard Street, Columbia Street, Tiffany Place and Kane Street, President Street.
  - INT Raw space, Green Terminal, Gowanus Industrial Park, Columbia Street off Halleck Street, Red Hook, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Red Hook Houses, Richards Street and Wolcott Street, Red Hook, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - The Old Pioneer Bar and Beer Garden, 318 Van Brunt Street (Red Hook), 2004 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Motor Inn, 140 Hamilton Avenue, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - EXT Stephen Crane Project, Red Hook East, West 9th Street and Clinton Street and Columbia Street, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - EXT/INT Gantry Crane, American Stevedoring, Inc., Red Hook Marine Terminal, 70 Hamilton Avenue, Red Hook, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Beard Street North, 4th Floor, Beard Street at Van Brunt Street, Red Hook, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Lillie's, 46 Beard Street (between Dwight and Otsego Street), 2004 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Sunny's, 253 Conover Street, between Beard Street and Reed Street (Red Hook), 2004 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - EXT Loft, Revere Sugar Corporation, 280 Richards Street, Red Hook, circa 2005 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - 26 Reed Street, circa 2005 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Verona Street between Van Brunt Street and Richards Street, circa 2005 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Union Street between Van Brunt Street and Columbia Street, circa 2005 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Coffey Street between Conover Street and Ferris Street, circa 2005 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn Grain Terminal, 699 Columbia Street, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - INT Apartment, 101 Dikeman Street, Red Hook, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - INT Apartment, 169 Dikeman Street, Red Hook, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Red Hook, Van Dyke Street and Ferris Street, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Warehouse, New York shipyards, 1 Bear Street, Red Hook, 2007 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - INT Bathroom, Red Hook Pool, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - EXT Josh's Neighborhood, Van Brunt Street, Red Hook, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - INT Old Man Black (Hearing Aid), 26 Reed Street, circa 2010 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - I/E Machine Shop, 145-165 Wolcott Street at Conover Street, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    This location was scouted for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close. This folder includes photographs of Perfect Bodies Auto Collision, Q. P. Fleet Services, 21st Avenue Transportation Company.
  - Kidd-Yellin, Red Hook Labs, 133 Imlay Street (between Verona Street and Pioneer Street), 2011 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - INT/EXT Apartment, 97 King Street (at Richards Street), Red Hook, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Waterfront Pier, Gowanus Grainery, Beard Street at Otsego Street, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - INT/EXT Black Bar, 200 Columbia Street, Miknic Bar, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - INT/EXT Machine Shop, 54 Richards Street at Delavan Street, Red Hook, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - INT/EXT Garage - Various Blacks, 34 Coffey Street at Dwight Street, Red Hook, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Waterfront, Cornell Paper Warehouse, 162 Van Dyke Street (at Ferris Street), 2011 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - INT/EXT apartment, 370 Van Brunt Street (at Wolcott Street), Red Hook, 2011 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Apartment, 396 Van Brunt Street (at Coffey Street), Red Hook, 2011 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - INT/EXT Apartment, 93 King Street at Richards Street, Red Hook, 2011 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Series 39: Sheepshead Bay, 1987-2004
  Series 39: Sheepshead Bay includes photographs of nightclubs, restaurants, and houses in the Sheepshead Bay neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Michael's Catering, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - INT Nightclub, Rasputin, 2670 Coney Island Avenue (at Avenue X), circa 1995 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - 2375 East 23rd Street (between Avenue W and Avenue X), Sheepshead Bay, circa 1995 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Liman Restaurant, 2710 Emmons Avenue between East 27th Street and East 28th Street, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Series 40: Sunset Park, circa 1980 - 2011
  Series 40: Sunset Park includes photographs of restaurants, bars, bowling alleys, churches, funeral parlors, industrial and manufacturing areas, and streets in the Sunset Park neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - 2nd Avenue to 3rd Avenue above 59th Street, circa 1980 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - 2nd Avenue to 3rd Avenue below 59th Street, circa 1980 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Army Supply Base, 1946, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    This folder includes a photocopied photograph of the Brooklyn Army Supply Base in 1946. This folder was categorized under "Industrial Parks."
  - Environs of Brooklyn Army Terminal (including Alex/Willie's Bar), circa 1988 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Union Hall, circa 1989 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Bush Terminal below 1st Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Bush Terminal, Loft number 2, Dock number 9, circa 1990 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Industry City, 39th Street and 2nd Avenue, 41st Street and 2nd Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - 47th Street between 2nd Avenue and 3rd Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT Bar, Muscarella's Marine Tavern, 718 3rd Avenue (at 23rd Street), Sunset Park, circa 1990 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Diner, N+P Donut Shop, 606 5th Avenue, Greenwood Heights, circa 1990 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - EXT Neighborhood, [61st] Street between 3rd Avenue and 4th Avenue (off Gowanus Expressway), Sunset Park, circa 1990 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Brooklyn Army Terminal, 58th Street, circa 1990 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Bush Terminal (Union Hall), circa 1990 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Bush Terminal (below 1st Avenue), circa 1990 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Brooklyn Army Terminal, circa 1990 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT Funeral parlor, Leone Funeral Home, 696 4th Avenue at 21st Street, Sunset Park, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - INT/EXT Funeral parlor, Las Rosas Funeral Home, 761 4th Avenue (between 25th Street and 26th Street), Sunset Park, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - EXT Ferrari driving, Bush Terminal area, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Bay Royal Towers, 420 64th Street between 4th Avenue and 5th Avenue, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - INT/EXT Industrial laundry, 262 59th Street at 3rd Avenue, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Various Exteriors, Brooklyn, circa 1995 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    This folder includes photographs of 52nd Street and 1st Avenue, 34th/33rd Street and 2nd Avenue, 36th Street and 2nd Avenue and 3rd Avenue, 34th Street and 3rd Avenue and 2nd Avenue, 33rd Street and 2nd Avenue and 3rd Avenue, 33rd Street and 2nd Avenue and 3rd Avenue, 34th Avenue and 35th Avenue and 2nd Avenue, 53rd Street and 1st Street (ConEdison Gas Turbine Department), 54th Street and 1st Avenue and 2nd Avenue.
  - Piers, Bush Terminal, circa 1995 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Bush Terminal (night), circa 1995 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Gas Station, 4th Avenue and 30th Street, 833 4th Avenue, circa 1995 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - S+S Machinery, 2 52nd Street, Sunset Park, circa 1995 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Diner, George's Restaurant, 156 5th Avenue, Greenwood Heights, circa 1995 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - INT Nightclub, Spectrum, 802 64th Street, circa 1995 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Storefront, 6th Avenue at 23rd Street, Corner Auto Repair, circa 1995 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - EXT Chez Bar, 23rd Street and 3rd Avenue [Muscarella's Marine Tavern Bar and Grill], 1995 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Rainbow Café, 3904 5th Avenue and 39th Street, Sunset Park, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Pier, Kamco Supply Corporation, 80 21st Street, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - 25th Street Pier, Dealer Storage Corporation, 75 25th Street, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Three Star Bar, 6th Avenue and 20th Street, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - INT Bar, 5th Avenue at 62nd Street, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - INT Sheriff's apartment, 692 5th Avenue, 3rd Floor, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Sunset Park, 39th Street and 40th Street at 4th Avenue, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Warehouse/Industrial area, 41st Street and 1st Avenue, 49th Street (between 1st and 2nd Avenues), 1997 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Chinese restaurant, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    This folder includes photographs of the Ocean Palace Restaurant at the corner of 8th Avenue and 35th Street.
  - Warehouse Industrial Area, 39th Street and 1st Avenue, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Warehouse, Industrial Area, 43rd Street at 1st Avenue, Bush Terminal, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Industry City, Bush Terminal, Loft #4, Hamilton Avenue [3rd Avenue], 35th Street, Sunset Park, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Industry City, Bush Terminal, Loft #4, Hamilton Avenue [3rd Avenue], 35th Street, Sunset Park, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - EXT NYC driving, Battery Tunnel Brooklyn/Manhattan (night), 1998 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Melody Lanes, 461 37th Street, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Hospital, Lutheran Medical Center, 150 55th Street (between 1st Avenue and 2nd Avenue), 1999 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - The Dock, NY and NJ Port Authority, Continental Terminals, 23rd Street and 3rd Avenue, circa 2000 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Industry City area, 2 warehouses, Sunset Park, circa 2000 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Prudential Lines, 39th Street, circa 2000 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - EXT Streets, Sunset Industrial Park, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    This folder includes photographs of 1st Avenue between 53rd Street and 54th Street, 1st Avenue at 45th Street, 2nd Avenue at 36th Street, 2nd Avenue at 36th Street.
  - 3rd Avenue and 25th Street, motel possibility, 754 3rd Avenue, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Sunset Park hotel possibilities, 2nd Avenue and 42nd Street, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - New College Cafe, 224 4th Avenue (at Union Avenue), Sunset Park, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Warehouse, Hollywood East, S+S Machinery Corporation, 140 53rd Street, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - 234 4th Avenue (at Union Street), Sunset Park [Delicias del Caribe], 2004 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Brooklyn Army Terminal, 140 58th Street and 1st Avenue, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - EXT/INT Bowling, Melody Lanes, 461 37th Street and 5th Avenue, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - INT Warehouse/Shop space, S+S Machinery Company, 140 53rd Street (between 1st and 2nd Avenue), Sunset Park, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Pier 53 Restaurant, 5513 2nd Avenue (between 53rd Street and 54th Street), Sunset Park, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Jimmy's Restaurant, 680 3rd Avenue (at 21st Street), Sunset Park, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - 2nd Avenue Deli, 5416 2nd Avenue (between 54th Street and 55th Street), Sunset Park, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - EXT cemetery, Green-wood Cemetery, 500 25th Street, circa 2005 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - 23rd Street between 3rd Avenue and 4th Avenue, circa 2005 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Army Terminal, entrance on 58th Street and 1st Avenue, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Bush Terminal between 38th Street and 32nd Street on 1st Avenue, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - South Brooklyn Marine Terminal, 39th Street at 1st Avenue, Sunset Park, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - EXT Church, Grace Baptist Church, 5224 6th Avenue, Sunset Park, circa 2007 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - INT/EXT School, P.S. 136, 4004 4th Avenue (between 40th Street and 41st Street), 2007 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - EXT Church, Kimisis Theotokou Greek Orthodox Church and Soterios Ellenas School, 224 18th Street at 5th Avenue, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - EXT North Korea, Brooklyn Army Terminal, 140 58th Street, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Army Terminal, 140 58th Street, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - EXT Train tracks, 65th Street railyard (Brooklyn Army Terminal), 140 58th Street, 2009 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - EXT German loft, Bush Terminal, 2nd Avenue, Sunset Park, circa 2010 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Sunset Park Warehouse Row, 35th Street to 31st Street (between 2nd Avenue and 3rd Avenue), 2011 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Brooklyn Army Terminal, 140 58th Street, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Series 41: Vinegar Hill, circa 1985 - 2011
  Series 41: Vinegar Hill includes photographs of apartments, houses, restaurants, and streets in the Vinegar Hill neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - La Playa de Ponce [Vinegar Hill], circa 1985 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - City Island Diner [1922 Bridge Street], circa 1985 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - 243 Front Street, circa 1990 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - EXT Ferrari driving, Brooklyn Warehouse Area, John Street (from Gold Street to Bridge Street), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Residence, 231 Front Street, 6th Floor, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    This location was scouted for Mr. Wonderful.
  - INT Amanda's Apartment, 239 Front Street, Vinegar Hill, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Vinegar Hill, Water Street and Hudson Avenue, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 249 Front Street Apt. 2, 1997 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - INT Townhouse EXT House, 24 Evans Street (at Little Street), Vinegar Hill, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Lano's Family Cafe, 73 Bridge Street, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    This location was categorized under "Brooklyn Bars and Diners."
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 239 Front Street, circa 2005 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Front Street and Gold Street, circa 2005 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - EXT 6th Borough, Vinegar Hill, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    This location was scouted for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close. This folder includes photographs of Hudson Avenue, Front Street, Water Street, Plymouth Street, Gold Street.
  - Black Day, Vinegar Hill, 49 Hudson Avenue at Plymouth Street, circa 2010 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Angry Woman Black, Vinegar Hill, 311 Water Street at Hudson Avenue, circa 2010 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - INT Old Man Black (Hearing Aid), 52 Hudson Avenue, circa 2010 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - INT old man Black (hearing aid), 260 Water Street, Apt. 5D, Vinegar Hill, circa 2010 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - 241 Front Street, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - INT Old Man Black (Hearing Aid), 77 Hudson Avenue, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - INT Old Mr. Black (Hearing Aid), 324 Plymouth Street, Apt. 2, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - INT Old Mr. Black (Hearing Aid), 87 Hudson Avenue, Apt. 3, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - INT Old Mr. Black (Hearing Aid), 237 Front Street, Apt. 1, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - INT Old Mr. Black (Hearing Aid), 53 Hudson Avenue, Apt. 2, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Series 42: Windsor Terrace, circa 1990 - 2003
  Series 42: Windsor Terrace includes photographs of a social club, gas station, and streets in the Windsor Terrace neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Social Club, 6th Avenue at 20th Street, circa 1990 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - EXT/INT Gas Station, McDonald Avenue at Seeley Street, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Windsor Terrace neighborhood, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    This folder includes photographs of Bartel-Pritchard Square.
- Series 43: Williamsburg, circa 1985 - circa 2010
  Series 43: Williamsburg includes photographs of delapidated buildings, manufacturing and industrial warehouses, apartments, restaurants, social clubs, schools, churches, and streets in the Williamsburg neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - South 10th Street between Bedford Avenue and Division Avenue, Williamsburg, circa 1985 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Williamsburg Streets, Williamsburg Bridge shots, South 6th Street & Driggs Avenue area, circa 1988 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - EXT chase, Pepper steals Mustang, 4 G's Truck Renting Co. Inc., 395 Kent Avenue at Broadway, circa 1990 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - EXT Car chase, Williamsburg [4 G's Truck Renting Co.], circa 1990 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Kent Avenue and South 2nd Street, Williamsburg, Domino Sugar, circa 1990 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Social Club, Metropolitan Avenue at Leonard Street, circa 1990 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Williamsburg Bridge, Brooklyn side, circa 1990 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Williamsburg Bridge area, various streets, circa 1990 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Neighborhood street, Metropolitan Avenue and Lorimer Street [Williamsburg], circa 1990 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Williamsburg Bridge Promenade, NYC side of bridge, circa 1990 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - EXT Warehouse area, Kent Avenue at North 11th Street, Williamsburg, circa 1990 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - EXT Dumping of Pop Fly, Kent Avenue between North 9th Street and North 10th Street, Williamsburg, circa 1990 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - The Motion Lounge, Graham Avenue and Wythe Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - EXT Ferrari driving shots, Williamsburg Bridge Area, Williamsburg, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - EXT Derelict Hotel, 176 South 8th Street between Driggs Avenue and Roebling Street, lot is 173-175 South 9th Street, Williamsburg, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - EXT Derelict Hotels, 14, 7 Dunham Place, 27, 35 Broadway, Williamsburg, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - EXT Derelict hotels, South 6th Street at Broadway, Williamsburg, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - EXT Derelict Hotel (former Keap Hotel), 306 Keap Street at Broadway, Williamsburg, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - EXT / INT Derelict Hotel, 103 Broadway, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - EXT Derelict Hotels, 100 Broadway at Berry Street, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - EXT Derelict Hotel: 115 Division Avenue between Bedford Avenue and Driggs Avenue, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - EXT Derelict Hotel, 152 South 9th Street at Driggs Avenue, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - INT Sweatshop, 85 North 3rd Street between Kent Avenue and Wythe Avenue, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Empire State Coat and Apron, 236 Stagg Street at Bushwick Avenue, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Wythe Avenue between South 3rd Street and South 4th Street, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - EXT Dumping of Pop Fly, 372 Kent Avenue, end of South 6th Street, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Williamsburg Art and Historical Center, 135 Broadway at Bedford Avenue, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 233 Bedford Avenue, Williamsburg, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    This location was scouted for Return to Paradise. This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn apartments."
  - Kent Avenue at North 1st Street, Williamsburg, circa 1995 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - South 6th Street (between Wythe Avenue and Dunham Place) Williamsburg, circa 1995 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 81 North 7th Street Apt. 1R, Williamsburg, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 597 Driggs Avenue, 2nd Floor, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    This location was scouted for Return to Paradise and considered for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close
  - Frost Restaurant [193 Frost Street, Williamsburg], circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - INT Coffee Shop: Sabrina's Place, 85 Broadway at Berry Street, Williamsburg, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - EXT Williamsburg Bridge, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - EXT Park Bench, McCarren Park, North 12th Street between Driggs Avenue and Bedford Avenue, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - INT Italian Restaurant, Bamonte's Restaurant, 32 Withers Street between Union and Lorimer, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - INT Sheriff's apartment, 179 South 2nd Street, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Cafe Right Bank, 409 Kent Avenue (between South 8th Street and Broadway), Williamsburg, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Williamsburg Bridge entrance, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - South 5th Street at Kent Avenue, Williamsburg, circa 1995 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Berry Street at North 8th Street, Greenpoint, circa 1995 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - EXT Dumping of pop fly, North 5th Street at Kent Avenue, circa 1995 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - EXT Dumping of Pop Fly: Grand Street at River Street on East River, Williamsburg, circa 1995 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - EXT Dumping of pop fly, Kent Avenue at North 10th Street, Williamsburg, circa 1995 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Pool Hall / Bar, Teddy's, 96 Berry Street at North 8th street, circa 1995 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Social club, Driggs Avenue at Fillmore Place, circa 1995 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Storefront/Social club, Valentine Studio, Richardson Street and Lorimer Street, Williamsburg, circa 1995 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Williamsburg - Neighborhoods/Lofts, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 6)